Do you like somewhere a little bit different to the usual types of places you find on the high street?
你喜欢那些与你在商业街常见的地方稍微不同的地方吗？
I do, so I'm glad to see new ones popping up everywhere in London.
我喜欢，所以我很高兴看到伦敦到处都涌现这类新地方。
The so called pop-up shop is a temporary arrangement.
所谓的快闪店是一种临时的商业形式。
In the aftermath of the financial crisis of 2008, many businesses had to shut down.
在2008年金融危机之后，许多企业不得不倒闭。
Shops, warehouses and offices were left vacant when they stopped trading.
商店、仓库和办公室在停止营业后都被空置了出来。
Pop-up entrepreneurs occupied some of them quickly.
快闪店的创业者们迅速占据了其中一些地方。
For them the appeal of this temporary shopping concept is clear: they can start a business with much lower risk.
对他们来说，这种临时购物概念的吸引力很明显：他们可以以低得多的风险开展业务。
The temporary nature of a pop-up gives the opportunity to test a product and develop a customer base, without being tied in to a long-term renting contract.
快闪店的临时性提供了一个测试产品和发展客户基础的机会，而且无需受限于长期租赁合同。
Being small makes it much easier for pop-ups to expand if they are successful.
规模小使得快闪店如果经营成功，扩展起来会容易得多。
Pop-up shops first appeared in the UK in the early 2000s, with the economy booming.
快闪店最早在21世纪初英国经济繁荣的时候出现。
They were originally a way for small, niche companies to rent retail space in great locations.
它们最初是小型的、针对特定小众市场的公司在黄金地段租赁零售空间的一种方式。
This was while landlords who owned these spaces looked for permanent tenants.
与此同时，拥有这些空间的房东则在寻找长期租户。
Pop-up shops can take a number of different forms.
快闪店可以有许多不同的形式。
They might be temporary shops in the high street or a shopping centre.
它们可能是商业街或购物中心里的临时店铺。
They might be simple market stalls.
也可能是简单的市场摊位。
They could be based in some kind of transport, like a food truck.
它们还可能基于某种交通工具，比如餐车。
Or they could be run by people who visit different establishments, like travelling chefs who take over pub and restaurant kitchens temporarily.
或者它们可能由那些会前往不同企业的人来经营，比如临时接管酒吧和餐馆厨房的巡回厨师。
According to a 2014 report by the Centre of Economic and Business Research, the pop-up industry was worth £2.1bn and is expected to grow by 8.4% this year.
根据经济与商业研究中心2014年的一份报告，快闪店行业价值21亿英镑，预计今年将增长8.4%。
Almost anything that can be on a high street can also be a pop-up.
几乎任何能出现在商业街上的业态都可以成为快闪店的形式。
There have been pop-up shops, art galleries, theatres and restaurants among others.
已经出现过快闪商店、艺术画廊、剧院和餐馆等等。
In an age of fast-changing habits, the pop-up idea might be here to stay.
在一个习惯快速变化的时代，快闪店的概念可能会一直存在下去。